Chandler Love

Munich, Germany • +49 176 54601273 • clove20123@gmail.com

• Portfolio • LinkedIn

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- React
- React Native
- JavaScript
- Non-Relational

Databases

Relational

Databases

- Node.js
- Angular
- TypeScript
- Bootstrap
- Express
- Visual Studio
- Microsoft

Office

- Git
- Unit Testing
- End-To-End

Testing

Integration

Testing

<u>Junior Full-Stack web developer</u> with a background in sales. Ability to produce well organized code. Experienced with crafting UI designs for websites. Able to create backend APIs with non-relational and relational databases. Fast learner with outstanding problem-solving skills. Focused on customer satisfaction and customer retention.

CURRENT WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

07/2021-Present

- Working for a local osteopathy practice to deploy a website for their business
- Used HTML and CSS to create a slick, modern, and easy to navigate website with multidevice and browser accessibility
- Continually making improvements and updating the website to stay on top of trends
- o Constantly in contact with the practice to improve customer satisfaction

PROJECTS

- Created a Pokedex App using JavaScript to display details fetched from an external API into a modal
- Made a client-side movie application using Angular and TypeScript that allows users to create an account and search for movies
- o Constructed another client-side (React) and server-side (API) movie application that additionally allows users to filter movies and delete their account
- Designed a chat app using React Native which enables users to chat, send pictures, and share their location

EXPERIENCE

01/2016-06/2019

SENIOR SALES ACCOUNT MANAGER, CHARLOTTE MOTOR SPEEDWAY

- Managed a portfolio of over 1140 accounts and acted as the point of contact to handle any customer needs
- o Maintained a trusted advisor relationship with key accounts to better fulfill their demands
- Trained junior staff members in using the company's software to boost efficiency
- Supervised staff from prospecting to closing to broaden the customer base
- Analyzed customer behavior and experience in order to improve future business relationships with customers, ultimately driving sales growth

05/2012-12/2015

JUNIOR SALES ACCOUNT MANAGER, CHARLOTTE MOTOR SPEEDWAY

- Guided customers through the purchasing process to increase customer satisfaction
- Clarified customer inquiries, regarding event schedules & details, ticket and event pricing, payment plan options, ticket insurance and return policies
- o Diagnosed customer complaints to help resolve issues efficiently

EDUCATION

02/2021-12/2021

FULL-STACK WEB DEVEOLPER, CARERRFOUNDRY

- Server-Side Programming & Node.js
- Client-Side Programming and React
- o Testing in the Development Process
- Native App Development and React Native
- Collaboration and Documentation

08/2010-12/2015

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BUISNESS ADMINISTRATION, UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA AT CHARLOTTE

- Major: Management Information Systems
- o Minor: Operations & Supply Chain Management